Whoa, I'm tired.
Gods above.
Everyone?
Seriously?
Why do you choose to put me through such trials?
We good starting with a round of juicy love stories?
Quit making it sound like you're ordering a round at the bar.
Okay, me first!
Yuka it is.
Do you have a boy crush, Yamada?
Ignorance is strength, I guess.
Seems like.
Huh?
Wait, what's that mean?
Why are you laughing like this?
No, really, I don't know.
What's that mean?
Hi!
Then how about this?
What sort of guys do you find hot?
Huh?
Gods above!
Oh, Gods above!
Well, huh? What sort of guy?
Uh, I guess the interesting sort?
Saw that coming. She's always saying that.
And I guess a guy who's kind of like a cat?
You've lost me.
What else?
Uh, enough about me. What about all of you? Do you have stories?
Like, have any of you been asked out already?
Yeah.
Same here.
Well, me too, then.
I haven't.
One of these girls is lying.
Two, I'd say.
Quit the psych test.
But you know what? Getting asked out is pretty childish anyway.
What? Wait, what do you mean?
Real adults let things slowly brew between each other until they find themselves unmistakingly in that sort of relationship.
Or something close.
They let it brew?
Sounds dumb.
Uh, well, I...
I prefer to get asked out for real!
What's the matter?
No, nothing. I just don't really get how to let things brew.
Oh, well, you see, it's...
Before they even start dating?
Flauché.
You mean S-E-X.
Adults treat it like it's some kind of recreational sport.
It's how they decide if they really want to go out.
I'm turning the lights off before we get in trouble.
Okay.
This is bad. I gotta break out of here.
Maybe I can just wait until they all fall asleep.
But if they notice I'm not in my room upstairs, all hell will break loose.
Huh?
S-E-X.
Now what?
Ah! This is bad!
Don't think those wayward thoughts!
Come on!
Two, three, five, ten!
Wait! What are the prime numbers again?
Hey.
Huh?
Do you think...
That I'm all...
Grown up?
What?
Huh?
Wait!
Now?
Here?
For real?
Oh!
I want to talk to you...
About something...
Oh!
Huh?
Is something the matter, Yamada?
No?
Nothing?
Wait.
Hold on a sec.
Your blankets are huge!
Crap!
I'm done for!
Huh?
AHHHHH!
Um...
Help me down!
What the...
You wanted to say something...
I do.
But It can wait till later...
And so, just like that, we made it to our group free time on the second day.
Now that's a vibe!
Foxy Fox!
Foxy Foxy Fox!
Will you stop?
You're ruining the mood!
For your information, these are holy grounds!
They say if a couple passes through here holding hands, they'll be bound together for eternity!
What, really?
That sure caused your interest, didn't it?
Fox!
Not getting any searches on that.
Who asked you to look it up?
Fox!
I'm telling you though they really…
I told her we'd talk, but…
Foxy Foxy Foxy Foxy Foxy Foxy Foxy Foxy Foxy!
How do I bring the audition up?
Foxy Foxy Foxy!
Foxy Foxy Foxy Foxy Foxy Foxy Foxy Foxy Foxy Foxy Foxy Foxy Foxy Foxy Foxy Fox Foxy Foxy Foxy Foxy Fox!
What do I even want to talk about?
Fatsy!
How I don't want her worrying about me?
How I want her to focus on work?
I don't know.
Just, if she's only here for my sake,
then I couldn't possibly take it.
Fatsy!
Come on, let's go!
Okay.
I wonder what else there is.
We haven't had much alone time.
Yeah.
So? You having fun?
I mean, more than I expected to.
Huh?
That's good, then.
That's...
I'm happy to hear it.
What does that mean?
What?
Just what I said.
Happy and fun.
Okay.
Then what's that face for?
Um, no...
No reason.
You had something booked, didn't you?
Yeah, sorry.
Why are you sorry?
I just can't pretend at it anymore.
I just...
really wanted to...
enjoy our school trip...
with you.
I...
I thought if you were having fun,
then I would eventually too.
But...
all I keep thinking about is the audition.
Can you believe how self-centered I am?
You know...
I'm kind of relieved.
I'm sorry.
You probably don't know how to react to this at all.
Turning her back on her job brings her to tears.
She can't just switch off work mode.
That's the way she is, and why I...
Why I...
Come on, hold it together!
I'm stronger than you think.
Oh...
Yes...
I was alone.
But I was fine with it.
To me,
the world seemed like nothing more than a filthy mess.
I was a hollow shell.
Pathetic.
And weak.
I thought that...
Everyone was laughing at me.
And making fun of me deep down.
I didn't think a single person wanted to talk to me.
I thought that was just the way things were.
But...
I made friends.
Friends like Arachi, Ota, and Kanzaki.
I sometimes talk with Kuganuma and the guys now.
I can even talk somewhat normally with girls.
Our teachers still irk me sometimes.
But I don't hate them.
Where I saw nothing before at school,
bit by bit,
I've started noticing things.
Happy things.
Sad things.
Embarrassing things.
Surprising things.
The once empty world.
Started to fill with color.
I'll admit it.
I like school.
I still would even without you around.
How could you say...
But...
It's only because you were.
You showed me this world.
You helped me.
See how beautiful it is.
Because you're in it.
I like you.
It's true.
I'd lost sight...
Of even the regular ordinary everyday.
Found out!
Prepare the celebration!
Come on!
What?
Were they just holding hands?
Oh, you think so?
Ever since I met Yamada,
even the everyday mundane
feels somehow special.
Maybe this is going too far.
But it feels like...
Yamada has made me who I am now.
I just...
I want to be the smallest...
Timiest...
part of her life.
And maybe this is going too far, but it feels like Yamada has made me who I am now.
I just... I want to be the smallest, tiniest part of her life.
Go for it. Your audition.
Huh?
It's tomorrow, right? You can still make it in time.
Yeah, but I...
Hop on the next bullet train. I'll tell the teachers you had to leave.
Take these.
That should be enough to get you there.
So this is why your bag was so full?
Sia...
About what you said!
Uh...
I'm just...
Glad to see that you're still you.
I want to...
To say it out loud as well.
Oh.
So...
Uh, Yamada?
She?
Everyone's all worked up saying you're missing!
You changed your mind on going to the audition, didn't you?
Here.
You're going to want to practice, right?
I'll put it in here for you.
I'll even pack these snacks for you!
Talk about that!
I'll handle things here.
Okay.
Save the tears for later.
Now get your butt moving!
Right. Thank you.
Yamada!
You'll be fine.
Shoot!
That was not the sort of thing I should say in front of Kobayashi!
Ugh...
Can hardly call myself a real leader after just ditching my group like this.
I wouldn't say that.
Thanks.
Oh!
Yikes!
I really gotta get back!
I really gotta think of an excuse.
Maybe I'll say I walked Yamada to the station because she had an emergency.
No, that's basically putting the blame on her.
Big congratulations!
No, no!
Mr. Seek, what?
What is it?
They're a couple!
But they aren't even in the same class!
Please!
Listen to me!
Hey!
Can you please stop this?
Seriously, stop it right this minute.
Yeah.
Sorry.
Haras, as strong as they come.
There.
Hmm...
Maybe this will do?
Hello!
Make sure you get me something good, okay?
I don't want some dumb keychain of a Robo-Kyo Mizudera with someone hopping off!
Make it good like that Gio Needle oil blotting paper!
And those Jari Manchu snacks and the Ron Ron scented sachets!
And maybe a bottle gourd while you're at it?
Okay...
Let me just see...
What's your deal, man?
Nothing.
Huh?
Just a present for my sister.
Oh!
For your sister?!
Why's that make you more interested?
No.
Uh.
Ugh.
Um.
Uh.
Um...
You got to fix it.
Back that up!
Uh.
Yamada called her parents right away who then called the teachers and so she
made it safely to her audition. It's fun enough even without Namada around
still listen to me our trip isn't over until you're all back home even still I just want to be with her
but where's our usual spot what does she mean
where
she couldn't mean
You're brave coming in here out of uniform. Did you get it right away? Not really
Lots to choose from
although
With all your illicit snacking here. I figured the library
You're on the books for it and all
That pun was unintentional, okay
So your audition
What?
I mean, I still don't know. I did my best but
That's good, right?
What is it?
This time around
Showed me that I still have so much to learn and
A lot of growing left to do
That's not true at all
Always wishy-washy
Jealous of people
Thinking negative thoughts that get me anxious
Honestly, honestly, I'm a real mess
Honestly, I'm a real mess
But I truly like who I am
I think I finally realized that about me now
And so
That's the reason
Everything around me is now so lovely
So special
And so important
Kyotaro Ichikawa
You made me realize who I truly am
So, Kyotaro Ichikawa
You're more important than anything
More special than anyone
You're my everything
I love you
So, do you
Wanna go out with me, then?
Boy, I'm...
Oh...
I...
Ow!
I really am messed up in the head.
There's no way any of this is real, yet even still.
This is how I, how we fell in love.
This is how I fell in love.